

Maithilee Borgaonkar

Inside Sales Specialist

About My Career

I have over 9 years of experience in the IT industry as an IT Sales Professional operating extensively in the US, UK, Europe, and the Middle East regions. My primary responsibilities include lead generation via email marketing and LinkedIn marketing, database creation, CRM management, handling timely follow-ups with clients, upselling, cross-selling, building sales pipelines, and discovering new lead generating channels.

Expertise Skill

- Lead Generation
- Email Marketing
- Database creation
- CRM/Database management
- Linkedin Marketing
- Lead Nurturing
- Customer Relationship Management
- Up-Selling & Cross-Selling

Contact Details

- +46-764366921
- maithileeborgaonkar@gmail.com
- Surtsögatan 3, 1104, Kista, Stockholm, 16442

Education

- 2013-2015
 MBA-Marketing
 Maharashtra Institute of Technology, Pune,
 India
- 2009-2012
 BBA-Marketing
 IPS Academy, Indore, India

Work Experience

- Senior Business Development Executive IGT Solutions | Feb, 2023-Present Gurgaon, India
- Senior Business Development Executive Evoke Technologies Pvt. Ltd. | 2022-2023 Hyderabad, India
- Senior Business Development Executive
 Encora Innovation Labs Pvt. Ltd. | 2019-2022
 Pune. India
- Senior Business Development Executive
 Systango Technologies Pvt. Ltd. | 2018-2019
 Indore, India
- Senior Business Development Executive Computronics India Pvt. Ltd. | Mar 2018-Nov, 2018 Indore, India
- Client PartnerZogato Tech Pvt. Ltd. | 2016-2018Pune, India
- Associate Business Consultant
 Mindbowser InfoSolutions Pvt. Ltd. | 2015-2016
 Pune, India

Certifications

- Six Sigma Green Belt certified
- Certification of Basic Automation
- Digital Marketing Certified
- Stock Market certification

Interests

- Painting.
- Calligraphy.
- Listening to music.

Personal Details

- Date of Birth- 1st July, 1991
- Gender-Female
- Marital Status- Married
- Nationality- Indian
- Work Status- Eligible to legally work in Sweden